the solution for this is that in cycle
13 we have already issued all the
instructions so no issue will happen we
have already begun execution of all
these instructions so the correct answer
obviously will not be that something
else executes in 13 because we already
have begun execution we have already
seen that these begin executing
entertainment but that's not the
question writing of the results neither
of these can write the result in 13 and
all the other results have already been
written for commit however this result
has been written in 12. this is the very
first instruction that we are going to
try to commit so this com this
instruction will actually commit in
cycle 13. so the correct answer is c for
commit one because this is the
instruction that commits
so this is also what happens in cycle
13.